[
    {
        "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
        "optionA": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "optionB":  "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
        "optionC": "Home Tool Markup Language",
        "optionD": "Hyper Tool Markup Language",
        "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out in HTML5?",
        "optionA": "placeholder",
        "optionB": "required",
        "optionC": "validate",
        "optionD": "mandatory",
        "answer":  "required"
    },


    {
        "question": "Which attribute is used to specify the URL of the image in HTML?",
        "optionA": "src",
        "optionB": "url",
        "optionC": "link",
        "optionD": "href",
        "answer": "src"
    },


    {
        "question": "What does CSS stand for?",
        "optionA": "Creative Style Sheets",
        "optionB": "Cascading Style Sheets",
        "optionC": "Computer Style Sheets",
        "optionD": "Colorful Style Sheets",
        "answer": "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which CSS property is used to control the text size of an element?",
        "optionA": "font-size",
        "optionB":  "text-size",
        "optionC": "size",
        "optionD":  "font-style",
        "answer": "font-size"
    },

    {
        "question": "In CSS, which property is used to control the space between the elements' border and its content?",
        "optionA": "margin",
        "optionB": "padding",
        "optionC": "spacing",
        "optionD": "border-spacing",
        "answer": "padding"
    },

    {
        "question":"Which CSS property is used to control the space between lines of text?",
        "optionA": "spacing",
        "optionB": "line-height",
        "optionC":"line-spacing",
        "optionD": "text-spacing",
        "answer": "line-height"
    },

    {
        "question": "In CSS, which property is used to set the text color of an element?",
        "optionA":  "color",
        "optionB":  "text-color",
        "optionC": "font-color",
        "optionD": "text-style",
        "answer": "color"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which CSS pseudo-element is used to style the first letter of a text?",
        "optionA": "::before",
        "optionB":  "::first-letter",
        "optionC": "::after",
        "optionD": "::first-line",
        "answer": "::first-letter"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which CSS pseudo-class is used to select an element when it's being hovered over by the mouse pointer?",
        "optionA":  ":hover",
        "optionB":  ":active",
        "optionC":  ":focus",
        "optionD":":visited",
        "answer": ":hover"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the result of the following expression: 3 + 2 + '7'?",
        "optionA": "327",
        "optionB": "12",
        "optionC": "57",
        "optionD": "5",
        "answer":"57"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which keyword is not used to redeclare and reinitialize variables in JavaScript?",
        "optionA": "var",
        "optionB": "let",
        "optionC": "const",
        "optionD": "variable",
        "answer": "const"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which operator is used to concatenate strings in JavaScript?",
        "optionA":  "&",
        "optionB": "+",
        "optionC": "*",
        "optionD": "-",
        "answer": "+"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does the `typeof` operator in JavaScript return for the `null` value?",
        "optionA": "'null'",
        "optionB": "'undefined'",
        "optionC": "'object'",
        "optionD": "'string'",
        "answer": "'object'"
    },

    {
        "question": "What will the following code output: console.log(2 + '2' - 1);",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "22",
        "optionC":"1",
        "optionD": "NaN",
        "answer": "21"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array in JavaScript?",
        "optionA": ".pop()",
        "optionB":".shift()",
        "optionC":".slice()",
        "optionD": ".splice()",
        "answer": ".pop()"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which operator is used for strict equality comparison in JavaScript?",
        "optionA":"==",
        "optionB": "===",
        "optionC":"!=",
        "optionD": "!==",
        "answer": "==="
    },


    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a function in JavaScript?",
        "optionA": "function",
        "optionB": "method",
        "optionC":"def",
        "optionD": "func",
        "answer":  "function"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which statement is used to exit a loop in JavaScript?",
        "optionA": "exit",
        "optionB": "return",
        "optionC":"break",
        "optionD": "continue",
        "answer":  "break"
    },


    {
        "question": "Which method is used to handle the success case of a Promise?",
        "optionA":".then()",
        "optionB":".catch()",
        "optionC":".finally()",
        "optionD":".success()",
        "answer": ".then()"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which method is used to handle errors in a Promise?",
        "optionA":".then()",
        "optionB":".catch()",
        "optionC":".finally()",
        "optionD": ".error()",
        "answer": ".catch()"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used inside an `async` function to pause execution until a Promise is settled?",
        "optionA":"pause",
        "optionB":"await",
        "optionC":"delay",
        "optionD":"stop",
        "answer": "await"
    }
]